{
    "id": "d6ecb5683d4b410e8e0a35c20829f77e",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "As Tom was suffering from fever, he ...................... go to work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can't",
                "couldn't",
                "won't"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He speaks as if he knows the truth. (Perhaps he does.)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "knows",
                "knew",
                "has known"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Rekha was clever enough to see ...................... the scam.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "across",
                "through",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is .................... old to walk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She was ....................... angry that she said nothing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "very",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Are you not ashamed ....................... your conduct?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "of",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The older you get, .......................... you become.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wise",
                "wiser",
                "wisest",
                "the wiser"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "No sooner had I opened the book, ...................... I started feeling sleepy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "before",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The room was .................... small to accommodate the guests.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The night was ....................... dark that I couldnâ€™t see anything.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Booker was ......................... timid to speak up.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "......................... being ill, she went to work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "However",
                "Though",
                "In spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I .................. taller.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am",
                "was",
                "have been"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}